addictioncenter.com 2019-04-04

# Privacy Policy - AddictionCenter

## The Addiction Center Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy was last modified on 4/25/16

This Privacy Policy applies to your use of addictioncenter.com (the “Website”) and contains Recovery Worldwide, LLC’s (“Owner” or “we”) policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of your data and content when you use the Website.

By using this Website, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and to the collection and use of information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy may change over time, but any future changes will not affect data that was collected under a previous version of this Privacy Policy. If any modifications substantially change your rights, we will provide notice on the Website.

### Information Collection and Usage

Upon registering to use the Website, we may ask you to provide us with information such as your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or business name and other such credentials that are necessary to authenticate users, validate user actions, or communicate with users. We collect this information from you when you subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form or call a phone number listed on the Website. We will not use this information for any other purpose than providing you with the information requested by you through the Website. You may, however, visit the Website anonymously.

We do not collect any information about you from other sources outside of your interaction with the Website or when you call a phone number listed on the Website. We will not share your data or content with anyone without your express consent and only to the extent necessary to provide you with the products and/or services requested. We will not sell or otherwise transfer your data or content to advertising platforms, data brokers, information resellers, or any other third-party organizations. Additionally, we will not use your data or content for advertising, marketing or similar services.

### How We Use Your Information

We do not collect any Personally Identifiable Information (“PII”) _[1] _from you unless you voluntarily choose to disclose such information while using the Website or contact us via e-mail or telephone call.

  * In order to take advantage of certain services and features on the Website, you must provide certain PII and Anonymous Information[2].
  * If you submit PII to us through the Website, then we may use your PII to improve our services to you, and to identify and authenticate your access to the Website’s services. In addition, we use Anonymous Information in aggregate form to build higher quality, more useful services by performing statistical analyses of the collective characteristics and behavior of our users to personalize your experience on the Website.
  * We may provide PII and Anonymous Information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies, or other unaffiliated businesses or persons for the purpose of processing such information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information in compliance with our Privacy Policy, and we use reasonable efforts to limit their use of such information and to use other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.
  * We may use your e-mail address to send you notifications and information that are related to your use of the Website, answer your questions about the Website, or fulfill a legal or regulatory disclosure requirement.

We may share your data and/or content if we believe that disclosure is reasonably necessary to comply with a law, regulation, valid legal process (e.g., subpoenas or warrants served on us), or governmental or regulatory request, to enforce or apply the Terms of Service, to protect the security or integrity of the Website, and/or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Owner, its employees, users, or others. If we are going to release your data, we will do our best to provide you with notice in advance by e-mail, unless we are prohibited by law from doing so. We may also disclose or transfer your data or content in connection with the sale, merger, bankruptcy, sale of assets or reorganization of our company. We will notify you if a different company will receive your data or content and the covenants in this Privacy Policy will apply to your data as transferred to the new entity.

The Owner is not attempting to provide any type of health advice or analysis to users. The Website is simply presenting users with information regarding substance abuse and treatment centers. Users should not interpret the Website’s display of this data as any type of assessment from it. Owner will not be held responsible for any assessment or decision users make based on the data presented in the Website.

### Data that You Direct Us to Share

You can direct us to share your data with other parties. Once you direct us to share your data and/or content with a third party, that data is governed by the third-party’s privacy policy. You can revoke your consent to share with the third party at any time.

### Owner’s Policy For Children

Owner does not wish to interact with or collect any data from individuals under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect any PII data from children under the age of 13. We request that minors do not engage with our Website without the consent of a parent or legal guardian, unless otherwise permitted by the law. If you are under the age of 13, please do not attempt to use the Website or send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or e-mail address. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to or on the Website. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. We encourage parents to monitor their children’s Internet usage and/or to use web filtering technology to supervise their children’s access to the Internet.

### Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

Some of our Website pages may utilize “cookies” and other tracking technologies like pixel tags and web beacons to improve the functionality of the Website. Cookies are text files that are sent by servers to web browsers and stored on your computer. They tell us which parts of the Website you’ve visited so we can alert you to software compatibility issues and save your preferences for future visits to the Website. Web beacons and pixel tags are images embedded in a webpage or e-mail for the purpose of measuring and analyzing usage and activity. The Website, or third party service providers acting on our behalf, may use web beacons and pixel tags to help us analyze usage and improve our functionality. Some cookies and other technologies may serve to recall PII previously provided by a user.

### Third-Party Links

The Website may contain links to third-party websites placed by us as a service to those interested in this information. Your use of all such links to third-party websites is at your own risk. We do not monitor or have any control over, and make no claim or representation regarding third-party websites. To the extent such links are provided by us, they are provided only as a convenience, and a link to a third-party website does not imply our endorsement, adoption or sponsorship of, or affiliation with, such third-party website. When you leave the Website, the terms of this Privacy Policy no longer govern.

### When You Contact Us For Help

Whenever you contact Owner for help, we collect your name and e-mail address along with additional information you provide in your request so that we can provide you with assistance and improve the Website.

### Security

The privacy and security of user data is as important to us as it is to you. We maintain strict physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that are designed to controls and protect your data from unauthorized access. We adhere to accepted industry privacy standards and comply with our own privacy practices.

In addition, we use strong encryption and a protocol for transmitting private information via the Internet. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Therefore, while we follow accepted industry standards and implement reasonable security practices to protect PII, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

### How Does Owner Handle Data From International Visitors?

The Website is hosted and operated entirely in the United States and is subject to United States law. Any personal information that you provide to Owner is being transferred to Owner for use solely in the United States and will be hosted on United States servers. You consent to the transfer of your personal information to the United States. If you are accessing the Website from outside the United States, please be advised that United States law may not offer the same privacy protections as the law of your jurisdiction.

### Changes to This Privacy Policy

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. In the event of a change, we will notify you by posting the new privacy policy on the Website. We advise you to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy will become effective once it has been posted on the Website. We will never change this Privacy Policy or the Terms of Service to allow the collection of your PII, data and/or content or make any other substantial changes without first getting your consent.

### Online Privacy Policy Only

This Privacy Policy applies only to information collected through the Website and does not apply to information collected offline through other communication mediums.

### Google Analytics

We are currently using Google Analytics to understand the Website’s audience and how we can tailor the content of the Website to best serve your needs. No PII is collected by Google Analytics. For more information on Google’s privacy policy, please [click here](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/).

### NOTICE FOR CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS

Under California Civil Code Section 1789.3, California users are entitled to the following consumer rights notice: If you have a question or complaint regarding the Website, please send an e-mail to contact@addictioncenter.com. You may also contact us using the information below.

Further, because we value your privacy, we have taken the necessary precautions to ensure that the Website is compliant with the California Online Privacy Protection Act.

### Contact Us

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us.

Recovery Worldwide, LLC  
Addiction Center  
424 E. Central Blvd., # 636  
Orlando, Florida 32801  
contact@addictioncenter.com

[1] **“Personally Identifiable Information”** means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to postal address, telephone number, fax number and e-mail address.  You will be asked to provide Personally Identifiable Information under various circumstances when using the Website, including when registering for services or when submitting an inquiry form to the Website.

[2] **“Anonymous Information”** means information which does not enable identification of an individual user, such as aggregated information about the use of the Website and its services.
